In this lesson we're going to take advantage of
在这节课 我们将使用
SageMaker's hyperparameter tuning functionality.
SageMaker 的超参数优化功能
Essentially, what SageMaker can do for us is
SageMaker 可以帮助我们
train a bunch of different models and choose the best one.
训练一批不同的模型 然后选择最佳模型
Of course, we are going to have to tell SageMaker how many a bunch is,
当然 我们需要告诉 SageMaker 一批是多少
and what we mean by best model.
以及最佳模型的标准是什么
To start with, let's remind ourselves how SageMaker trains a model.
首先回忆下 SageMaker 如何训练模型
I'm going to open up the batch transform, XGBoost, high-level notebook.
打开 XGBoost (Batch Transform) - High Level notebook
I've already opened it up and run the first few cells,
我已经打开它并运行了前几个单元格
and the important ones here are in step four when training the XGBoost model.
重要的是第 4 步 训练 XGBoost 模型
Remember, what we do is we first create an estimator object and this kind of
我们首先创建了一个 estimator 对象
acts as a wrapper for the parameters that we're going to use to construct our model.
充当构建模型时将使用的参数的封装器
We then set parameters that are specific to the model that
然后指定模型的参数
we've chosen in our case because we've chosen XGBoost,
我们选择使用 XGBoost
these are some of the hyperparameters we wish to set and then we call
所以将超参数设为这些值
the fit method and SageMaker takes care of
然后调用 fit() 方法
creating a training job and executing it for us.
SageMaker 将创建并执行训练作业
So, how do we know that these hyperparameters are
如何知道这些超参数
the best hyperparameters for the model that we are working on?
是模型的最佳超参数？
The answer is basically trial and error.
答案是反复试验
We would maybe change this to six or change this to 0.3 or 0.05,
可以将这个改为 6 这个改为 0.3 或 0.5
we'd make some modifications here,
修改下这些值
and then we would train the model another time,
再训练一次模型
and then we would check to see whether the metric that we're using in this case
然后看看当我们更改这些超参数时
RMSE has decreased when we change these hyperparameters.
我们设定的指标（我们使用的是 RMSE）是否降低了
This is a very iterative process where we're just sort of plugging in new numbers
这是一个不断迭代更新的过程 我们只是代入新的数字
up here and training the model again and
然后重新训练模型
checking the output and since that's very routine,
看看输出结果 因为这个过程很流程化
we would hope that there would be an automated way of doing this, and there is.
所以我们希望有个自动化过程 的确有
This is what SageMaker's hyperparameter tuning does.
这就是 SageMaker 超参数优化的职责
So, instead of giving Gamma say a parameter value of four we would give it a range of
与其将 gamma 参数设为 4
values and then SageMaker would try different values in
我们将提供一个值范围 SageMaker 会尝试该范围内的不同值
that range and then using by default Bayesian optimization,
然后 默认情况下使用贝叶斯优化方法
it would find the optimal or attempt to find the optimal value for Gamma.
寻找 gamma 的最优值
Optimal in this case is going to depend on
最优值取决于
whatever training metric we use to differentiate different trained models.
我们比较不同训练模型时用到的训练指标
Before we see how to do this,
在学习如何优化之前
I just want to take a moment to talk a little bit about this output that we see here.
我先讲讲这段输出内容
When a training job successfully completes part of what is displayed here is the output
当训练作业成功执行完毕后 这里显示的部分内容是
that the Docker container containing
XGBoost 算法运行所在的 Docker 容器
the XGBoost algorithm that was running output to standard output.
输出的标准输出结果
Sometimes when you get an error,
有时候 当你遇到错误时
you don't get this output in the notebook.
Notebook 中不会出现这个输出结果
This output still exists,
这段输出依然存在
however, to look it up,
但是要查看它
you need to use something called CloudWatch,
需要使用 CloudWatch
which I'm going to show you in a moment.
稍后我会讲解 CloudWatch 的
In order to use CloudWatch,
为了使用 CloudWatch
we need to look at the logs that were generated by a specific training job.
我们需要查看特定训练作业生成的日志
In this case, scrolling all the way up to the top we can
一直滚动到顶部
see that the name of the training job is this one right here.
可以在这里看到训练作业的名称
So, now if we open up the SageMaker console and we'll look under
打开 SageMaker 控制台
training jobs we will see right here at the top is the training job that we just created.
点击“Training jobs” 在右侧顶部可以看到刚刚创建的训练作业
Selecting this and scrolling down,
选择这个作业 向下滚动
we see that there is a section called Monitor.
可以看到有个部分叫“Monitor”
In particular, there's a link called the View logs.
这里有个“View logs”链接
If we click on this it will open up the logs
点击它将在 CloudWatch 中
for this particular training job inside of CloudWatch.
打开此训练作业的日志
So, now, if I select this,
选择该日志
it will give me a list of all of
就可以看到
the output that was generated during this training process.
在此训练过程中生成的所有输出列表
As I said before, this can be
正如我之前提到的
a very useful way to diagnose issues that might arise when training a model.
通过这些日志可以很好地诊断在训练模型中可能会出现的问题
It's also useful when you have a deployed model if it starts acting strangely,
此外 如果部署的模型行为变得奇怪时
the errors may appear here in CloudWatch.
错误可能会出现在 CloudWatch 日志中
Also, when working on the project,
此外 在处理项目时
you'll note that you can include some of your own custom code,
可以添加自定义代码
and if you wanted to, you could print output
还可以使用自定义代码输出结果
using that custom code and it would appear here in the logs.
输出会出现在此日志中